BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VIII: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6758: Safeway Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 400, 1960-1962 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Safeway Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 400, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 36)
      Agreement effective 1/31/1960 and expires on 3/3/1962. Covers an unknown number of workers in Washington, D.C.
  - Code no.6759: St. Paul Food Retailers Association of Greater St. Paul and Retail Clerks International Association Local 789, 1959- 1971 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: St. Paul Food Retailers Association of Greater St. Paul and Retail Clerks International Association Local 789, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 37)
      Agreement effective 2/23/1959 and expires on 2/22/1962. Covers 1200 workers in St. Paul, MN
    - Item 2: St. Paul Food Retailers Association of Greater St. Paul and Retail Clerks International Association Local 789, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 37)
      Agreement effective 2/23/1962 and expires on 2/22/1965. Covers 1600 workers in St. Paul, MN
    - Item 3: St. Paul Food Retailers Association of Greater St. Paul and Retail Clerks International Association Local 789, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 37)
      Agreement effective 2/23/1965 and expires on 2/22/1968. Covers 1500 workers in St. Paul, MN
    - Item 4: St. Paul Food Retailers Association of Greater St. Paul and Retail Clerks International Association Local 789, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 38, Folder 37)
      Agreement effective 2/23/1968 and expires on 2/27/1971. Covers 1600 workers in St. Paul, MN
  - Code no.6760: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Retail Clerks' International Association, 1960-1969 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Retail Clerks' International Association, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 03/07/1960 and expires on 02/10/1962. Covers 6500 workers in New England.
    - Item 2: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Retail Clerks' International Association, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 02/12/1962 and expires on 08/08/1964. Covers 6500 workers in New England.
    - Item 3: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Retail Clerks' International Association, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 08/10/1964 and expires on 11/12/1966. Covers 6500 workers in New England.
    - Item 4: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Retail Clerks' International Association, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 11/14/1966 and expires on 11/15/1969. Covers 6500 workers in New England.
  - Code no.6761: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, 1960-1966 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 03/07/1960 and expires on 02/10/1962. Covers 1800 workers in Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and Connecticut.
    - Item 2: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 02/12/1962 and expires on 08/08/1964. Covers 1800 workers in Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and Connecticut.
    - Item 3: Stop and Shop, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 08/10/1964 and expires on 11/12/1966. Covers 1800 workers in Massachusetts, Rhode Island, and Connecticut.
  - Code no.6762: Kroger Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1099, 1960-1971 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Kroger Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1099, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 05/01/1960 and expires on 05/05/1962. Covers 1650 workers in Ohio, Kentucky, and Indiana.
    - Item 2: Kroger Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1099, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 05/06/1962 and expires on 05/01/1965. Covers 1850 workers in Ohio, Kentucky, and Indiana.
    - Item 3: Kroger Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1099, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 05/02/1965 and expires on 05/04/1968. Covers 1600 workers in Ohio, Kentucky, and Indiana.
    - Item 4: Kroger Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 1099, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 05/05/1968 and expires on 05/01/1971. Covers 1900 workers in Ohio, Kentucky, and Indiana.
  - Code no.6763: Retail Meat Industry and Butchers Union Local 551, 1955-1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Industry and Butchers Union Local 551, 1955-1956; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 11/07/1955 and expires on 11/04/1956. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Southern CA.
    - Item 2: Retail Meat Industry and Butchers Union Local 551, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 11/02/1959 and expires on 11/01/1964. Covers unknown number of workers workers in Southern CA.
  - Code no.6764: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 439, 1955-1964 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 439, 1955-1956; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Item 2: Retail Meat Industry and Meat Cutters Local 439, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6766: Milwaukee Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 73, 1959- 1961 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Milwaukee Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 73, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 10/04/1959 and expires on 09/30/1961. Covers 1100 workers in Milwaukee, WI.
  - Code no.6771: American Stores Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 56, 195, 198, 199, 1959- 1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: American Stores Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 56, 195, 198, 199, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 06/01/1959 and expires on 11/30/1961. Covers 1100 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
    - Item 2: American Stores Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 56, 195, 198, 199, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 12/01/1961 and expires on 02/29/1964. Covers 3000 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
    - Item 3: American Stores Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 56, 195, 198, 199, 1964-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 03/01/1964 and expires on 02/26/1966. Covers 3900 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
    - Item 4: American Stores Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 56, 195, 198, 199, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 02/27/1966 and expires on 03/02/1969. Covers 3900 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
    - Item 5: American Stores Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Locals 56, 195, 198, 199, 1969-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 03/03/1969 and expires on 02/28/1971. Covers 3900 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
  - Code no.6772: Retail Meat Markets and Frozen Food Locker Plants and Butchers' Union Local 506, 1961-1967 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Markets and Frozen Food Locker Plants and Butchers' Union Local 506, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 10/29/1961 and expires on 10/24/1964. Covers 1400 workers in California.
    - Item 2: Retail Meat Markets and Frozen Food Locker Plants and Butchers' Union Local 506, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1964 and expires on 10/31/1967. Covers 1500 workers in California.
  - Code no.6773: Chain and Independent Grocery Stores in Houston and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of America Local 408, 1962-1966 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Chain and Independent Grocery Stores in Houston and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of America Local 408, 1962-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 01/08/1962 and expires on 11/01/1963. Covers 1250 workers in Texas.
    - Item 2: Chain and Independent Grocery Stores in Houston and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of America Local 408, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1963 and expires on 11/01/1966. Covers 1200 workers in Texas.
    - Item 3: Chain and Independent Grocery Stores in Houston and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of America Local 408, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6774: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1960-1972 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1960-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 07/23/1960 and expires on 01/25/1964. Covers 1500 workers in Baltimore, MD.
    - Item 2: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 01/26/1964 and expires on 01/27/1967. Covers 1500 workers in Baltimore, MD.
    - Item 3: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1967-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 01/22/1967 and expires on 07/19/1969. Covers 1300 workers in Baltimore, MD.
    - Item 4: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1969-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 07/20/1969 and expires on 07/17/1971. Covers 2500 workers in Baltimore, MD.
    - Item 5: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1971-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 07/18/1971 and expires on 08/26/1972. Covers 2500 workers in Baltimore, MD.
  - Code no.6775: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 880, 1961-1966 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 880, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/01/1961 and expires on 09/23/1963. Covers 1300 workers in Cuyahoga, OH.
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union Local 880, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 09/29/1963 and expires on 10/02/1966. Covers 1150 workers in Cuyahoga, OH.
  - Code no.6778: Retail Distribution Agreement in California and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 229, 1962- 1967 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Retail Distribution Agreement in California and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 229, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 11/05/1962 and expires on 11/02/1964. Covers 1200 workers in Western CA.
    - Item 2: Retail Distribution Agreement in California and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 229, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 12/18/1964 and expires on 11/01/1967. Covers 1200 workers in Western CA.
    - Item 3: Retail Distribution Agreement in California and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 229, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Code no.6779: Denver Retail Grocers and Retail Clerks Union Local 7, 1961-1964 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Denver Retail Grocers and Retail Clerks Union Local 7, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 01/01/1962 and expires on 10/31/1964. Covers 1700 workers in Denver, CO.
    - Item 2: Denver Retail Grocers and Retail Clerks Union Local 7, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 12/29/1961 and expires on 10/31/1964. Covers 1550 workers in Denver, CO.
    - Item 3: Denver Retail Grocers and Retail Clerks Union Local 7, 1963-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1963 and expires on 10/31/1964. Covers 1550 workers in Denver, CO.
  - Code no.6780: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Local 455, 1963-1969 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Local 455, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 02/03/1963 and expires on 02/05/1966. Covers 1250 workers in Houston, TX.
    - Item 2: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks Union Local 455, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 02/06/1966 and expires on 02/01/1969. Covers 1000 workers in Houston, TX.
  - Code no.6781: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 1063, 1657, 1963-1967 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 1063, 1657, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 04/29/1962 and expires on 05/01/1965. Covers 1000 workers in Atlanta, GA; Birmingham, AL.
    - Item 2: Kroger Co. and Retail Clerks International Association Locals 1063, 1657, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 05/02/1965 and expires on 05/04/1968. Covers 1160 workers in Atlanta, GA; Birmingham, AL.
  - Code no.6783: Northern Minnesota and Northern Wisconsin Food Merchants and Retail Clerks Local 1116, 1962-1968 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Northern Minnesota and Northern Wisconsin Food Merchants and Retail Clerks Local 1116, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 05/01/1962 and expires on 04/15/1965. Covers 1000 workers in Northern MN; Northern WI.
    - Item 2: Northern Minnesota and Northern Wisconsin Food Merchants and Retail Clerks Local 1116, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Item 3: Northern Minnesota and Northern Wisconsin Food Merchants and Retail Clerks Local 1116, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 04/15/1965 and expires on 04/15/1968. Covers 1000 workers in Northern MN; Northern WI.
  - Code no.6786: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council and Warehouse Employees' Union Local 169, 1959-1965 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council and Warehouse Employees' Union Local 169, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 07/01/1959 and expires on 06/30/1962. Covers 1900 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
    - Item 2: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council and Warehouse Employees' Union Local 169, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 07/01/1962 and expires on 07/03/1965. Covers 1900 workers in Philadelphia, PA.
  - Code no.6788: Food Retailers Association of Greater New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Retail Food Store Employees Local 342, 1964-1970 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Food Retailers Association of Greater New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Retail Food Store Employees Local 342, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 02/03/1964 and expires on 02/04/1967. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New York.
    - Item 2: Food Retailers Association of Greater New York and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Retail Food Store Employees Local 342, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 02/06/1967 and expires on 02/07/1970. Covers unknown number of workers workers in New York.
  - Code no.6789: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1625, 1963-1972 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1625, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 04/18/1963 and expires on 04/18/1966. Covers 1400 workers in Miami, FL.
    - Item 2: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1625, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 04/15/1963 and expires on 04/18/1966. Covers 1200 workers in Miami, FL.
    - Item 3: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1625, 1969-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 04/20/1969 and expires on 04/23/1972. Covers 2800 workers in Miami, FL.
    - Item 4: Food Fair Stores, Inc. and Retail Clerks International Association Local 1625, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 04/17/1966 and expires on 04/20/1969. Covers 2250 workers in Miami, FL.
  - Code no.6914: Ford Dealers Association and Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1967-1973 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Ford Dealers Association and Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 07/01/1966 and expires on 07/01/1969. Covers 618 workers in Chicago, IL.
    - Item 2: Ford Dealers Association and Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1969-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 07/01/1969 and expires on 07/01/1972. Covers 790 workers in Chicago, IL.
    - Item 3: Ford Dealers Association and Automobile Mechanics' Local 701, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 20)
      Agreement effective 07/01/1972 and expires on 07/01/1973. Covers 1030 workers in Chicago, IL.
  - Code no.6911: Shoe Retailers League, Inc. and Retail Shoe Employees Union Locals 1268 and 287, 1959-1968 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Shoe Retailers League, Inc. and Retail Shoe Employees Union Locals 1268 and 287, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 21)
      Agreement effective 09/01/1959 and expires on 08/31/1962. Covers 1000 workers in New York, NY.
    - Item 2: Shoe Retailers League, Inc. and Retail Shoe Employees Union Locals 1268 and 287, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 21)
      Agreement effective 09/01/1962 and expires on 08/31/1965. Covers 1000 workers in New York, NY.
    - Item 3: Shoe Retailers League, Inc. and Retail Shoe Employees Union Locals 1268 and 287, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 21)
      Agreement effective 09/01/1965 and expires on 08/31/1968. Covers 1000 workers in New York, NY.
  - Code no.6907: Retail Apparel Merchants Inc. and ACWA Local 340, 1960-1966 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Retail Apparel Merchants Inc. and ACWA Local 340, 1960-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 22)
      Agreement effective 09/01/1960 and expires on 08/31/1963. Covers 3000 workers in New York, NY.
    - Item 2: Retail Apparel Merchants Inc. and ACWA Local 340, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 22)
      Agreement effective 09/01/1963 and expires on 08/31/1966. Covers 3000 workers in New York, NY.
  - Code no.6906: Associated Mens' Wear Retailers of New York, Inc. and Retail Men's Wear, Sporting Goods and Accessories Employees' Union, 1958-1969 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Associated Mens' Wear Retailers of New York, Inc. and Retail Men's Wear, Sporting Goods and Accessories Employees' Union, 1958-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 12/22/1958 and expires on 09/30/1961. Covers 1200 workers in New York, NY.
    - Item 2: Associated Mens' Wear Retailers of New York, Inc. and Retail Men's Wear, Sporting Goods and Accessories Employees' Union, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 11/04/1964 and expires on 09/30/1967. Covers 2000 workers in New York, NY.
    - Item 3: Associated Mens' Wear Retailers of New York, Inc. and Retail Men's Wear, Sporting Goods and Accessories Employees' Union, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 23)
      Agreement effective 10/05/1966 and expires on 09/30/1969. Covers 2000 workers in New York, NY.
  - Code no.6905: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union, 1960-1967 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union, 1960-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 24)
      Agreement effective 12/01/1960 and expires on 12/01/1961. Covers 6300 workers.
    - Item 2: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union, 1962-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 24)
      Agreement effective 12/16/1962 and expires on 12/16/1963. Covers 6300 workers.
    - Item 3: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union, 1964-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 24)
      Agreement effective 10/01/1964 and expires on 10/01/1965. Covers 6546 workers.
    - Item 4: Standard Stations, Inc. and Western States Service Station Employees Union, 1966-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 24)
      Agreement effective 04/15/1966 and expires on 04/15/1967. Covers 4290 workers.
  - Code no.6904: Gasoline Service Stations and Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Industries Employees Union Local 618, 1958- 1963 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Gasoline Service Stations and Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Industries Employees Union Local 618, 1958-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 25)
      Agreement effective 11/01/1958 and expires on 10/31/1963. Covers 2800 workers in Missouri.
    - Item 2: Gasoline Service Stations and Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Industries Employees Union Local 618, 1958-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Item 3: Gasoline Service Stations and Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Industries Employees Union Local 618, 1958-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Item 4: Gasoline Service Stations and Automotive, Petroleum and Allied Industries Employees Union Local 618, 1958-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Code no.6903: Service Stations and IBT Local 705, 1959-1970 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Service Stations and IBT Local 705, 1959-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 39, Folder 26)